trendsbuzz.com 2011-10-07

# Trends Buzz - Privacy Policy

Trendsbuzz.com (“Trends Buzz”) operates the Trendsbuzz.com. It is Trends Buzz’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

## Website Visitors

Like most website operators, Trends Buzz collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Trends Buzz’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Trends Buzz’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Trends Buzz may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Trends Buzz also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. Trends Buzz does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below.

## Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to Trends Buzz’s websites choose to interact with Trends Buzz in ways that require Trends Buzz to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Trends Buzz gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we may in the future require users who wish to sign up for an Account with Trendsbuzz.com to provide a username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with Trends Buzz are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Trends Buzz collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Trends Buzz. Trends Buzz does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

## Aggregated Statistics

Trends Buzz may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, Trends Buzz may monitor the most popular searches on Trendsbuzz.com. Trends Buzz may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Trends Buzz does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

## Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

Trends Buzz discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Trends Buzz’s behalf or to provide services available at Trends Buzz’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Trends Buzz’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Trends Buzz will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Trends Buzz discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when Trends Buzz believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Trends Buzz, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an Trends Buzz website and have supplied your email address, Trends Buzz may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Trends Buzz and our products. We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Trends Buzz takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

## Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Trends Buzz uses cookies to help Trends Buzz identify and track visitors, their usage of Trends Buzz website, and their website access preferences. Trends Buzz visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Trends Buzz’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Trends Buzz’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

## Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Trends Buzz may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Trends Buzz’s sole discretion. Trends Buzz encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. If you have a wordpress.com account, you should also check your blog’s dashboard for alerts to these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
